Welcome back. How do you get your entire team rowing in the same direction,
on the same rhythm,
especially when everything feels like a priority?
The 90-Day Way is not just a personal tool.
It's a powerful framework for team alignment.
And there's a science to this.
Researchers have found that sports teams with
high levels of psychological predictability,
what we can think of as neurological alignment, simply perform better.
For leaders, this means alignment isn't just a strategy. It's a rhythm.
High-performing teams share a mental cadence that
maps directly to organizational trust and cohesion.
I saw a team completely transform when their manager used this.
Instead of juggling 10 priorities, she brought them together and asked,
what is the one thing we must achieve this quarter to be successful?
They decided on one critical initiative.
Every week, their check-in started with that goal.
They were more focused and collaborative.
Your play is to introduce this concept in your next team meeting.
Don't try to boil the ocean here.
Use the framework to facilitate a discussion
and set one shared 90-day goal with your team.
You can introduce the 90-Day Way, and a team member expresses skepticism,
seeing that it just is another corporate initiative.
How do you address their concern and build buy-in?
Your playbook contains a guide called Coaching Through Skepticism,
with talking points to help you navigate that exact moment.
Now that your team has a plan, what happens when they hit an obstacle?
In our final topic, we'll talk about this,
and we'll cover how to coach through roadblocks.
See you there.